<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<bug-report>
    <ID>
        Identification number assigned to a specific bug
    </ID>
    <Summary>
        Summarizes the essence of the bug in one sentence. Answers the questions «What?» Where?» Under what circumstances?
    </Summary>
    <Project>
        Name of project, program or application in which a bug is identified
    </Project>
    <Version>
        The exact version of the software containing the bug
    </Version>
    <Severity>
        <definition>
            The parameter that determines the effect of the bug on the program on a scale from S1 to S5
        </definition>
        <classification>
            <S1-Blocker>
                Blocking error. It makes impossible all subsequent work with the program. To resume work need to fix Blocker
            </S1-Blocker>
            <S2-Critical>
                Critical error. Disrupts the main functionality. Bug appears constantly and makes it impossible to use the main functions of the program
            </S2-Critical>
            <S3-Major>
                Significant bug. Complicates the work of the main function or makes it impossible to use additional functions.
            </S3-Major>
            <S4-Minor>
                A minor bug. The functionality of the system affects relatively little, makes it difficult to use additional functions. There may be obvious ways around this bug.
            </S4-Minor>
            <S5-trivial>
                Trivial bug. Does not affect the functionality of the project, but worsens the overall impression of working with the product.
            </S5-trivial>
        </classification>
    </Severity>
    <Priority>
        <definition>
            Parameter that determines the urgency of bug correction on a scale from P1 to P3
        </definition>
        <classification>
            <P1-Top>
                The highest priority. Assigned to emergency situations that have a very negative impact on the product or even the business of the company. Such bugs should be eliminated immediately.
            </P1-Top>
            <P2-High>
                High priority. Assigned to bugs, which must be eliminated first.
            </P2-High>
            <P3-Normal>
                The normal priority is assigned by default. These bugs are eliminated  secondarily.
            </P3-Normal>
            <P4-Low>
                Low priority. Assigned to bugs that do not affect the functionality. Fix such bugs last if there are time and resources
            </P4-Low>
        </classification>
    </Priority>
    <Status>
        What stage the bug is: open, in work, fixed, rejected, delayed, etc.
    </Status>
    <Author>
        Name of employee who found the defect
    </Author>
    <Attachments>
        Links, screenshots, videos and other materials that will help the developer better understand the nature of the problem
    </Attachments>
    <Assigned_to>
        The developer that will fix the bug
    </Assigned_to>
    <Steps_to_reproduce>
        The exact sequence of actions, which leads to reproduction of a bug
    </Steps_to_reproduce>
    <Actual_result>
        What happens when you play the steps, how the program works now
    </Actual_result>
    <Expected_result>
        How the program really should work
    </Expected_result>
</bug-report>
